const QuizData = [
  {
    Name: "football",
    QuestionsData: [
      {
        questionindex: "f-one",
        question:
          "Which of the following country won Football world Cup maximum times?",
        options: ["Germany", " Italy", "Argentina", "Brazil"],
        correct: "Brazil",
      },
      {
        questionindex: "f-two",
        question:
          "Who among the following player scores highest number of goals in Footbal World Cup?",
        options: ["Jurgen Klinsmann", "Maradona", "Miroslave Klose", "Pele"],
        correct: "Miroslave Klose",
      },
      {
        questionindex: "f-three",
        question:
          "Which of the following term is recognised as an early form of football by FIFA?",
        options: ["Kemari", "Episkyros", "Cuju", "Inuit"],
        correct: "Episkyros",
      },
      {
        questionindex: "f-four",
        question: "When was the first FIFA World Cup inaugurated?",
        options: ["1930", "1931", "1932", "1933"],
        correct: "1930",
      },
      {
        questionindex: "f-five",
        question: "Which of following team do not play in stripes?",
        options: [
          "Newcastle",
          "Southampton",
          "Tottenham Hotspur",
          "Lincoln City",
        ],
        correct: "Tottenham Hotspur",
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    Name: "basketball",
    QuestionsData: [
      {
        questionindex: "f-one",
        question:
          "Which of the following country won Football world Cup maximum times?",
        options: ["Germany", " Italy", "Argentina", "Brazil"],
        correct: "Brazil",
      },
      {
        questionindex: "f-two",
        question:
          "Who among the following player scores highest number of goals in Footbal World Cup?",
        options: ["Jurgen Klinsmann", "Maradona", "Miroslave Klose", "Pele"],
        correct: "Miroslave Klose",
      },
      {
        questionindex: "f-three",
        question:
          "Which of the following term is recognised as an early form of football by FIFA?",
        options: ["Kemari", "Episkyros", "Cuju", "Inuit"],
        correct: "Episkyros",
      },
      {
        questionindex: "f-four",
        question: "When was the first FIFA World Cup inaugurated?",
        options: ["1930", "1931", "1932", "1933"],
        correct: "1930",
      },
      {
        questionindex: "f-five",
        question: "Which of following team do not play in stripes?",
        options: [
          "Newcastle",
          "Southampton",
          "Tottenham Hotspur",
          "Lincoln City",
        ],
        correct: "Tottenham Hotspur",
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    Name: "cricket",
    QuestionsData: [
      {
        questionindex: "f-one",
        question:
          "Which of the following country won Football world Cup maximum times?",
        options: ["Germany", " Italy", "Argentina", "Brazil"],
        correct: "Brazil",
      },
      {
        questionindex: "f-two",
        question:
          "Who among the following player scores highest number of goals in Footbal World Cup?",
        options: ["Jurgen Klinsmann", "Maradona", "Miroslave Klose", "Pele"],
        correct: "Miroslave Klose",
      },
      {
        questionindex: "f-three",
        question:
          "Which of the following term is recognised as an early form of football by FIFA?",
        options: ["Kemari", "Episkyros", "Cuju", "Inuit"],
        correct: "Episkyros",
      },
      {
        questionindex: "f-four",
        question: "When was the first FIFA World Cup inaugurated?",
        options: ["1930", "1931", "1932", "1933"],
        correct: "1930",
      },
      {
        questionindex: "f-five",
        question: "Which of following team do not play in stripes?",
        options: [
          "Newcastle",
          "Southampton",
          "Tottenham Hotspur",
          "Lincoln City",
        ],
        correct: "Tottenham Hotspur",
      },
    ],
  },
];

export { QuizData };
